[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 7]
I have a question for you.
Not ashamed to ask,
you've become a good boy now.
Forget about it.
What's your question?
♫The trees and grass of the world sway with the wind♫
♫Beneath the bodhi tree, dust gathers♫
♫Who truly decides fate's design?♫
I beg you to ask.
♫Vividly painted in black and white♫
Wen Xiao seems
to be doing a lot better.
♫It's water under the bridge♫
Is it because...
You know what? Let's just drop it.
♫The moon sheds her light on my heart♫
You...
King Xiang wants us
back to report by noon.
Why are you walking so slowly?
♫The good old days are gone for good like that lantern in my dream♫
Do you wanna get killed?
-Your fault. -Your fault.
♫See immortals enter Penglai♫
Jiu!
Brother Zhuo!
I'm so glad to see you back.
I was freaked out!
I was waiting for you
in the Demon Hunting Bureau.
They said if you don't come back
to report by noon,
everyone will pay with their lives.
I was afraid you'd leave me and run away,
and I'd be the only one
to suffer in the Demon Hunting Bureau.
So I came out to welcome you
but accidentally
ended up in this mountain god temple.
There's a demon inside!
Let's go in and check.
Let's go.
Where's the demon?
Jiu.
No demons here.
There is one!
There's definitely one here!
No demons.
There is one.
Such a big one here.
It's not funny.
They've gone for quite a while.
Could they have run into trouble?
If they still don't come back,
you will be in big trouble.
There's only a quarter of an hour left.
The Demon Hunting Bureau
shall either hand in the closing document
or
kill those five persons,
This is my turf;
I am the boss.
If you want to pass...
Little brat,
ditching school
to be a bandit here?
Little?
♫Leaving home, going far away from those mountains♫
Who do you call little?
♫And that stream♫
♫The boy wiped away his tears and sang♫
♫He carried his dreams with him♫
♫Jingling all the way♫
♫Wind, rain, and light♫
♫Wandering with me♫
Little girl,
the temple is a solemn place.
Please be quiet.
Who are you calling "girl"?
Not a girl?
He's so short.
He just hit a nerve directly.
Why are you laughing?
I...
You really broke his heart,
boy.
Boy?
If I tell you my age,
you'll certainly freak out.
This man
is 34,000 years old.
It's this demon.
A thousand-year-old demon.
Who are you calling a demon?
Other than demons,
immortals are also as old as the hills.
Got it?
You're in a mountain god temple.
I
am the Mountain God, Yinglei!
If you dare to offend me in my place,
you'll end up
just like those people
crying out on the ground.
Who is he?
He sounds so full of himself.
Half a demon.
He is half-god and half-demon,
a scion of the Mountain God Yingzhao.
Did your grandpa let you
leave home so easily?
The Mountain God of the Wilderness
is already stuck in a mess
and has no time for me.
The Wilderness?
What happened in the Wilderness?
After the Baize Token disappeared,
the Wilderness began to collapse.
Grandfather and the others had to close
the Kunlun Gate
and cut off the connection
between the Wilderness and the mortal realm.
That's how the collapse was relieved.
But after that,
another monster appeared,
opening the Kunlun Gate by force
without authorization.
Then loads of demons flocked
into the mortal world,
causing chaos in both realms.
That's the root
of the further decreased and unsustainable
spiritual energy in Kunlun.
Grandpa and other Mountain Gods
had no choice but to use their divine power
to barely maintain stability.
But we don't know how long
they have to hold on.
Ugh,
so annoying.
It’s all that Baize Goddess's fault.
The Wilderness is about to collapse,
yet where is she?
You are really unfilial.
Your grandpa's fighting so hard in the Wilderness,
while you're making a fuss
in the mortal world, huh?
I'm not here for fun.
I'm here to realize my dream.
And my grandpa actually supports me.
Maybe he allowed me
to do it because he knew the Wilderness
would be doomed.
You come across
as even worse this way.
Who are you,
yapping here nonstop?
He is a great demon, for real.
Are you scared?
He feeds on those with beards like you.
I don't care if he's a great demon or not!
I'm the boss of this place!
-You know what... -Enough.
Why should we stop
to listen to two kids bickering?
Alright, stop it.
Show some respect
to those people over there.
They are here to kill us seriously.
Go!
Shoo,
shoo!
Hurry up...
Go!
Get up, or I'll kick you hard!
It's getting late.
Let's hurry up and hit the road.
What should we do
with this little demon in our way?
Do we have to deal with him?
If so, when it's done, the sun will set,
and I'll be dead.
This is the demon expert
in the Demon Hunting Bureau,
who specializes in catching little demons like you.
Mm,
delicate-skinned demons are good.
And half-god,
half-demon types like you
are even better.
You think you can beat me?
Kneel.
Move.
Stop.
Okay.
I give in.
What is it?
So powerful.
It numbed my whole body
and knocked me out.
I know your mountain god temples
keep myriad artifacts.
If you don't wanna be taken back
to the Demon Hunting Bureau to suffer,
just hand over
your treasures.
Fine...
My precious pepper.
What treasures are these?
Are you trying to fool us?
They are my treasures!
Treasures that lead me to my dream.
It took me a lot of effort to collect them.
You don't understand.
I'm carrying my dream every day.
Your dream
is to carry the wok?
It's to be a chef!
A top chef who makes delicacies
in the mortal world!
Everything's here.
Not these.
You mean this, right?
What is it?
An incense burner, I guess?
This is the artifact
that the Mountain Gods use
to teleport across hills and peaks,
called the Shanhai Portal.
With it,
we can rush back
to the Demon Hunting Bureau right away.
How to use it?
This is the Mountain God's artifact.
So of course,
it needs the Mountain God to cast a spell.
You just called me a little demon.
Now you call me the Mountain God.
So worldly.
And this is mine.
Why should I let you use it?
If you help us,
we will do you a favor too.
What favor?
I have neither desires
nor anxiety.
To help you realize your dream.
Don't you want to be a chef?
Our Demon Hunting Bureau
happens to need a chef.
You...
Don't you mind that I'm a demon?
You just called yourself a little Mountain God.
Of course, we don't mind it.
The Demon Hunting Bureau deals with demons every day.
And we have a large personnel,
requiring various delicacies every day.
We've also got servants
specifically responsible for buying
all sorts of fresh daily ingredients.
The whole kitchen
is as large as your mountain god temple,
providing a complete set of kitchenware.
She's right.
OK!
The Shanhai Portal
can only help you teleport to a place you know.
Have you been to the Demon Hunting Bureau?
Sure.
I've sneaked over there several times.
Let's begin.
Go!
♫First time being in this world♫
♫Let me enjoy all the splendors♫
♫Leaving home, going far away from those mountains♫
♫And that stream♫
♫The boy wiped away his tears and sang♫
♫He carried his dreams with him♫
♫Jingling all the way♫
♫Wind, rain, and light♫
♫Wandering with me♫
Looks like the Demon Hunting Bureau
can't solve the case.
In that case,
I'll send you to hell first.
Mr. Zhen Mei.
Mr. Fan Ying,
the Water Ghost case has been solved.
Our advance team of five
is back to report.
Let's wait and see.
Who is this?
Nice to meet you, sirs.
I'm Yinglei,
a newbie in the Demon Hunting Bureau as a...
A chef!
The Water Ghost case is over.
The Great Demon invited us
to his home in the suburbs of Tiandu
for a drink and celebration.
Sister Pei,
are you coming with me?
Even if you're leaving,
you should at least bid a proper farewell.
I've decided to stay
in the Demon Hunting Bureau.
What's wrong?
You don't want me to?
I'd love to hear that!
♫An arrow in the hand♫
♫A string in the heart♫
♫A backside standing, turning into forever♫
♫The moon shines on the south♫
♫But I look north♫
♫I only hope the snow comes a bit later♫
I didn't want to
get involved in demon stuff anymore.
♫Intimately bound together in the cold world♫
♫Even death can't break our ties♫
Or maybe I was just avoiding it.
♫Like intertwined fates, debt, love, and hatred♫
But in life
♫Reluctant but with no resentment♫
I see with my eyes,
♫Only half of the bows and arrows remain♫
listen with my ears,
and observe with my heart,
just to see through everything
♫Night and dawn are forever kept apart♫
and live a sober life.
♫If you were a spring night♫
♫I'm the silent mountain♫
So I've decided not to run away anymore.
♫You're a sad firefly♫
♫Guarding the last moment of night♫
♫Why don't you remember♫
The word "dawn"
♫I'm always by your side♫
has dawned on me.
♫Like wind surrounding flowers♫
♫Guarding the memories♫
♫Never fading away♫
The day breaks.
Thank you
for turning my dark night
♫Turns out I'm a wanderer♫
into a dawn.
♫And you're a song of reluctant parting♫
♫In the sky of floating snowflakes♫
♫You are the only warm bloom♫
♫But why don't I remember♫
♫How much the plot has twisted?♫
♫I forgot the bitter karma♫
♫I missed it again and again♫
♫Helpess♫
♫Turns out I'm a wanderer♫
♫And you're a song of reluctant parting♫
♫I'm a black and white wound♫
♫You're the vibrant red color♫
♫How can I not remember♫
♫You're always by my side♫
♫Like wind surrounding flowers♫
♫Guarding the memories, never fading away♫
Falling flowers,
permeating fragrance.
How is it?
Isn't my place pretty nice?
A seclusion in the bustling city,
adorned with natural beauty.
It is quite good.
But it doesn't feel like
the kind of place you'd live in.
Oh?
I specially opened the barrier
to welcome all of you.
Why are you so mean to me?
Then tell me, Mr. Zhuo,
where should I live?
The place you live
should have corpses, bones, and blood
all over.
That suits your image.
Only those soaked in blood
love bathing, burning incense,
and having flowers around.
After all these years in the mortal world,
my biggest gain
is to learn that
a human
should know how to hide his true self.
You're not human.
So sharp all of a sudden.
I didn't expect that.
Zhuo Yichen, Zhuo Yichen.
Zhao Yuanzhou, Zhao Yuanzhou.
Let's celebrate our teamwork
in solving the Water Ghost case.
The crisis of the Demon Hunting Bureau
has finally been settled.
The Demon Hunting Bureau survived,
and so did I!
Great!
Don't get carried away.
In the Demon Hunting Bureau,
you may lose your life at any time.
It's still not too late
to quit now.
I was a little scared before.
But our team
has Mr. Zhuo, the strongest one in Tiandu.
I'm not afraid anymore.
When we were in danger,
Mr. Zhuo
was always protecting me.
I can also protect you, too!
I’m the Mountain God!
Wen, hope you find
and get the Baize Token back soon.
Then, those demons and monsters
can't cause chaos in the mortal world
and hurt humans anymore.
No more tragedies like what happened
to Ran Yi and Miss Qi.
Mm.
With the Baize Token,
even the greatest demons are no big deal.
Brilliant.
I swear I'll help you
find and retrieve it, Wen.
Then my mom will...
What did you say?
Bai Jiu?
Nothing.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Why is it tea for me?
No alcohol for kids.
You call me a kid.
Then how old are you?
I should be 18
in human years.
Eight...
Eighteen?
Eighteen with this thick beard?
Guess it's time for a shave.
I'll sneak into Zhao Yuanzhou's room later.
He has no beard
at his age.
He must have a razor.
I'm gonna be ugly.
Mirror, mirror,
promise me.
Please remember
how handsome I look at over 200.
Well...
How can I refill my tea?
I also want it.
Come on.
A little.
That's enough.
Wow.
What is this?
A kid's meal I made
just for you!
Let me try.
How is it?
How's my cooking?
It tastes so good!
By the way, Yinglei,
I helped you realize your dream and become a chef
in the Demon Hunting Bureau.
So,
shouldn't you repay me?
No problem!
Help me steal Zhao Yuanzhou's bottle.
Well...
That's...
actually a big problem.
I'm just curious
what on earth is in his bottle.
This Great Demon hasn't
had anything the whole trip
but what's in his bottle.
I got you!
I've already sniffed out
what's in his bottle.
Jade bracelets!
Sir,
what kind of jade do you like?
I have no preference.
As long as it's jade.
OK...
Do you guys know
jade cream?
Jade cream?
According to the book,
the Mountain of Jade produces jade cream,
which, mixed with the powdered Heartless Herb,
can turn into liquid.
Drink it,
and you can become immortal.
Not that powerful.
That's to tease kids.
But having plenty of it
can prolong your life
and replenish your spiritual energy.
No wonder that Great Demon
holds his bottle every day
without letting go.
So it's really his food reserve.
The Great Demon
was just chatting with Mr. Zhuo.
But where is he now?
How about we make another bet?
Bet on what?
Let's see who's the first to solve
the water ghost bride abduction case.
The loser
should do one thing for the other.
Deal.
But that thing
should be within the loser's capabilities
and can't be immoral.
Keep your promise,
Mr. Zhuo.
You're pulling a long face.
Don't tell me you have zero tolerance
even for this.
Do you have eyes behind your back?
I'm looking great.
Wen Xiao and I were the first
to solve the water ghost bride abduction case.
You have such a poor memory, Mr. Zhuo.
You said it yourself
that I knew the murderer was Ran Yi
before I came to the Demon Hunting Bureau.
So I solved the case first, of course.
I admit defeat.
But you won unjustly.
You knew Ran committed a crime,
yet you still colluded with him.
You are accomplices.
Something's heavy on my head.
My neck hurts.
What's wrong with you again?
Someone put the "heavy" blame on me.
You...
I did this
because I know you too well.
Ridiculous.
We've only known each other for a few days.
You know me?
Dream on.
Everyone in Tiandu knows
Mr. Zhuo
is handsome
and charming.
You're like a sharp sword
when dealing with evil demons,
upholding justice,
sticking to principles,
and having ambition.
Right?
Indeed.
So,
if I had told you
the murderer Ran Yi's whereabouts,
the righteous Mr. Zhuo
would have left in no time
to arrest Ran for sure.
Then how could we find clues
about the Baize Token?
The less flexible it is,
the easier it is to break.
You can't stick to the rules too rigidly.
To achieve a goal,
sometimes we have to use special methods.
Mr. Zhuo,
am I right?
Flexibility is okay,
but not always tricks and schemes.
Could you push it for me?
Move.
You...
You hid Ran Yi's whereabouts
and even tried to drag us into your plan.
It's obviously deception.
Unfortunately, you are too smart.
My plan failed.
It doesn't mean you didn't do it.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
your eloquence
can deceive Zhuo,
but not me.
She means you're goofy.
I...
Despite
our different personalities
and ways of doing things,
we have the same goal.
So we should be honest with each other
and discuss more.
Trust
is like a swing.
You must trust the people behind you
to swing higher.
You are so good at pushing a swing.
Don't you understand that?
The little demon Ran Yi
is not dangerous.
What about Li Lun?
You hid the existence of Li Lun,
and he almost got Wen Xiao...
Li Lun wouldn't really kill her.
If Li Lun tried to kill Wen Xiao seriously,
you couldn’t stop him.
What is he up to?
I don't know.
It's always hard
to read his mind.
Move.
Mr. Zhuo, you quit?
Are you angry because I said
you're too rigid?
Didn't you just say
you only like sitting on the swing,
not pushing it?
Aren't you enjoying pushing it now?
Old liar.
So that's why you're mad.
Come here, then.
Let me push it for you.
Ridiculous.
Adults
are not obsessed with the swing!
He's mocking you.
Keep pushing.
Move.
They must be having fun with the swing, huh?
Mr. Zhuo
on the swing?
Bai Jiu just said you...
Is the wine good?
Not bad!
The pomegranate wine
from Tianxiang Pavilion
is indeed worthy of its reputation.
The smell is mellow and fragrant.
Little Mountain God,
you just came down the mountain
and already got so much info.
You even know Tianxiang Pavilion?
Yeah.
When I just left the mountain,
I heard that
Tianxiang Pavilion
was holding a beauty contest.
There must be good wine
as well as lovely girls.
I'm thinking about finding a chance
to have fun there one day.
If you go, I'll tell Sister Wen.
Unless you take me with you,
and I won't tell her.
You...
Drink some more.
C'mon...
No, thanks.
It's wet...
It's okay. I'll hang it up to dry.
Just a small patch is wet.
Why bother?
Sister Pei.
You don't
look so well.
[File]
There's another murder case in Tiandu.
Where is Wen Xiao?
She's on the swing
with Zhao Yuanzhou over there.
What do you want to say?
You would never
let Wen Xiao
be alone with him before.
Mr. Zhuo,
You're innocent and kind.
Don't easily
let down your guard against him.
I'll never let my guard down.
Is everything ready?
The file
has been delivered to Pei Sijing.
Thanks to you,
the fish took the bait.
Pei Sijing saw his face.
She will definitely investigate it.
It’s time to let them know
where the Baize Token is.
Aren’t you afraid that old demon
might kill them?
That old demon is indeed powerful.
I'm scared of him too.
But I want Zhao Yuanzhou and his crew
to suffer.
Can Zhao Yuanzhou really find the Baize Token?
According to the file,
since two days ago,
two households in Tiandu
have been murdered consecutively,
both happening at noon.
No signs of a struggle inside.
It's not a robbery.
Actually, there is another reason
why I'm investigating this case.
What is it?
This is the household
where the first murder occurred.
There's no demonic energy.
My sword is not shining.
I don't need you to tell me.
Yeah...
Awesome...
No blood,
nor signs of fighting.
It looks pretty normal.
It's just that no one is here.
Being too normal
is actually an anomaly.
Your Bingyi Clan's sense of humor
is hard to understand.
Give me your hand.
Is it necessary?
You're so scared.
Are you serious?
Let me borrow some demon blood of yours.
Last time at the Mirror Lake,
I found
your blood on the Yunguang Sword
made its power soar.
Is this the so-called “bloody bad luck”?
♫Can't tell tears from wine♫
♫So frustrating♫
♫The moon and the puppy go with me silently♫
♫Time never stops♫
Ouch...
It hurts...
♫The boy never looks back♫
♫He left his hometown and love behind♫
Why are we in the same squad?
Bloody bad luck...
What are you afraid of?
I'm here.
Let's go.
Is this their strategic arrangement?
In their eyes,
we're...
-Discarded pawns. -Aces.
Aren't you half-god, half-demon?
Are you actually half-pig-demon?
What do you mean?
I'm saying you're as dumb as a pig.
Jiu,
you...
You're getting better at mocking others.
No plum trees in the yard.
Where did these petals come from?
The plates are still warm.
That means...
The murderer is still here.
Sister.